Register of the Henry Regnery Papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Subject File, 1927-1978 (Box 81-82)
  Proposals, memoranda, clippings, articles, and reviews arranged alphabetically by topic. Includes a history of the Regnery Company.
  - Authors. Correspondence, 1959 1969 (Folder 81: 12)
  - Book reviews (Folder 81: 13)
  - Classics of Conservative Thought (Book series). Correspondence, 1967 (Folder 81: 14)
    - Gill, William J.
    - Loeffler, Theodore B.
    - Milbank, Jeremiah, Jr.
    - Terrill, Dean
  - College Conservative Movement, Union League Club Luncheon,., 1964 (Folder 81: 15)
    Correspondence, invitation and RSVP, 1963-1964
  - History of the Henry Regnery Company, 1950-1965 (Folder 81: 16)
    - Articles
      - "A New Voice from Chicago: The Background of Henry Regnery Company"
      - "Blacklist Agency's Henry Regnery Heads 'Captive Nations' Body,", 1960 July
      - "Fifteen Years of Publishing: Henry Regnery Company," Human Events, 1963 February 23
      - "Regnery Charges Censorship of Ideas," Book Industry, 1964 March
    - Biography,, two drafts, 1960
    - Correspondence, 1950-1963
      - Boveri, Margret A., 1963
      - Clark, Howard, 1953
      - Egan, Miss, 1950
      - Fitzpatrick, Edward A., n.d.
      - Jackson, Eugenia, 1964
      - Parrish, Thomas, 1954
      - Webster, Linda, 1960
      - Wick, James L., 1963
    - Memoranda
      - 1961 May
      - 1963 December
    - Notification of dissolution of Henry Regnery Company. Correspondence with Attorney General of Illinois, 1960
    - Press releases, n.d.
    - Reports
      - Catholic paperbacks
      - Circulation reports, 1950 January
      - Present status and future prospects, 1960 January and March
      - Esther Stamm's paper on the Regnery and Devin-Adair Company, 1965 March 24
  - Legal affairs. Correspondence, 1956-1961 (Folder 81: 17)
    - Schmidt and Tetreault, 1957
    - Scofield, Charles J., 1956
    - Sinclair, W. W., 1961
    - Tatge and Jersild, 1960
  - Miscellaneous, 1967-1969 (Folder 81: 18)
  - Oil companies. Correspondence, 1957 (Folder 81: 19)
    - Butterworth, E. (California-Texas Oil)
    - Drew, Warren (Gulf Oil)
    - Lockett, Charles (Standard Oil)
    - Philips, Thomas (Socony-Mobil Oil)
    - Thompson, H. O. (Arabian-American Oil)
  - Proposal for new series of books on education, international relations, government, economics. and society. Correspondence, 1958 (Folder 82: 1)
    - Couch, W. T.
    - Cowling, Donald
    - Crocker, George N.
    - Grede, William, Jr.
    - Lipsett, Don
    - Mason, Frank
    - Mayer, Ferdinand L.
    - Milliken, Roger
    - Moley, Raymond
    - Mullendore, W. C.
  - Publishers. Correspondence, 1966 (Folder 82: 2)
  - Reilly and Lee Company 25th Anniversary. Correspondence, 1927 (Folder 82: 3)
  - Travel, 1965-1967 (Folder 82: 4)
    - Log of trip to Europe, 1965 November 6-24
    - Washington D.C., 1966
    - Aspen, Colorado, 1967
- Photographs, 1964, undated
  - 18 prints of Henry Regnery at the Joanna Western Mills Old Timers' Banquet, the city of Trier in West Germany, and portrait photographs, October 1964 (Envelope A)
  - 5 prints of Virgil Gheorghiu and his wife at a gathering, undated (Envelope B)